# MohammadReza Tayyebi

Iran



tayyebimohammadreza@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mohammadrezatayyebi

#### Summary

IT project manager and software developer with Master of Business Administration (MBA) and Bachelor of Computer Engineering (CE) background. Experienced in architecture and development of clean, lite, and stable back-end APIs and high-frequency database queries. Skilled in installation, maintenance, and rescue of Microsoft Windows and Linux servers and some cloud technologies. Able to design and ensure the quality and time limitations of IT projects a deep understanding of business requirements such as finance, marketing, and human capitals. Comfortable with diverse teams in case of gender, professional background, nationality, position, approach, and work/life style.

Being among 45 selected students out of 25339 and awarded in the most creditable scientific festival of Iran, known as Khwarizmi, even before attending university. Also taken part in the most popular skill-based competition of the world, WorldSkills, in 2017.

#### **Experience**



#### 🇼 Founder

Gordarg 2016 - Present (7 years)



#### 🎳 IT Consultant and Web Developer

Universal Versatile Society Jun 2021 - Present (1 year 8 months)

### **Information Technology Consultant**

Plompin Sanat 2018 - Present (5 years)

### Project Manager

Tokan Tav Tejarat Jun 2022 - Dec 2022 (7 months)

## Back-end Developer (Remote)

مِستربليط | MrBilit

Jan 2021 - May 2021 (5 months)

Participation in code refactoring, API and database development, with multiple programming languages. Please contact for technical details due to NDA limitations.

### Project Manager

ATINET Co.

#### Guest Summer School Workshops Teacher

Bu-Ali Sina University

Jul 2019 - Sep 2019 (3 months)

Summer School, Student Scientific Society of Computer Engineering

### Project Manager

Rayan Electronic Andish Hegmataneh

Oct 2017 - Mar 2019 (1 year 6 months)

#### Expert

WorldSkills IRAN

May 2018 - May 2018 (1 month)

#### **Competitor**

WorldSkills International

2016 - 2017 (1 year)

#### **Education**



#### K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Master of Business Administration - MBA

Nov 2021 - 2023

### Bu-Ali Sina University

Bachelor of Science (BSc), Computer Engineering

2016 - 2020

#### Skills

Scrum • Business Analysis • Software Architecture • Risk Management • Human Resource

Development • Software Systems Engineering • Project Management • Microsoft SQL Server • MySQL • C#

#### **Honors & Awards**



Third Degree of Khwarizmi 16th Festival - Ministry of Education, Ministry of

Science Research and Technology, Iranian Research Organization for Science and Technology (IROST)

Dec 2014

The Khwarizmi (in Persian = خوارزمی) is the most important scientific festival in Iran. This festival contains "International" and "Young" groups. Anyone who gain any award in this festival, will be a member of "IRI Elites Foundation".

In 2014, about 25339 students with 20702 projects was introduced to the youth festival. After 3 levels of judgment by IRI Ministry of Education and the last judgment by Ministry of Science, There was 45 succeeded student with 33 projects.

#### First in WorldSkills National Level 2016 - TVTO

Feb 2016

Gold medal in national skills competition and candidate on WorldSkills 2017 AbuDhabi.

Field: 09 - IT Software Solutions for Business.

### Presence as Competitor, WorldSkills 2017 Abu-Dhabi - WorldSkills

Oct 2017

WorldSkills 2017 Abu-Dhabi

skill: 09, IT - Software Solutions for Business